let questions = [{
    num: 1,
    question: "Javascript is an _____language.",
    answer: "Object Oriented",
    option: [
        "Object Oriented",
        "Object Based",
        "Procedural",
        "None Of the above"
    ]
}, {
    num: 2,
    question: "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
    answer: "const",
    option: [
        "const",
        "var",
        "let",
        "constant"
    ]
}, {
    num: 3,
    question: "When an operator’s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
    answer: "Object",
    option: [
        "Boolean",
        "Object",
        "Undefined",
        "Integer"
    ]
}, {
    num: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not a Javascript framework?",
    answer: "Cassandra",
    option: [
        "Node",
        "Vue",
        "React",
        "Cassandra"
    ]
}, {
    num: 5,
    question: "Which function is used to serialize an object into a JSON string in Javascript?",
    answer: "stringify",
    option: [
        "stringify",
        "parse",
        "convert",
        "None of the above"
    ]
}, {
    num: 6,
    question: "What keyword is used to declare an asynchronous function in Javascript?",
    answer: "async",
    option: [
        "await",
        "async",
        "setTimeout",
        "None Of the above"
    ]
}, {
    num: 7,
    question: "How to stop an interval timer in Javascript?",
    answer: "clearInterval",
    option: [
        "clearTimer",
        "intervalOver",
        "clearInterval",
        "None Of the above"
    ]
}, {
    num: 8,
    question: "How do we write a comment in javascript?",
    answer: "//",
    option: [
        "/**/",
        "//",
        "#",
        "$$"
    ]
}, {
    num: 9,
    question: "Which of the following are not server-side Javascript objects?",
    answer: "all Of the above",
    option: [
        "Date",
        "FileUpload",
        "Function",
        "all Of the above"
    ]
}, {
    num: 10,
    question: "Which object in Javascript doesn’t have a prototype?",
    answer: "Returns a localized string representation of an object.",
    option: [
        "Returns a localized string representation.",
        "Returns a parsed string",
        "Returns a localized string representation of an object.",
        "None Of the above"
    ]
}]